

AURORA GEORGES

aurorageorges@hotmail.com | +49 15147106852 | 13407 Berlin Brusebergstrasse 33, GERMANY | www.aurorageorges.com

PROFILE

Bachelor degree in Digital Art and Design at Hedmark University of Applied Sciences, with almost 4 years of combined experience as a 2D Artist working in the mobile game-industry. Specialized in character design, concept art and illustration, with basic understanding of 3D sculpting, 2D animation and Unity. Fast learner, motivated and passionate artist with a strong desire to create artwork for games.

EXPERIENCE

DEC 2021 - CURRENTLY

JUNIOR 2D CONCEPT ARTIST, TAP4FUN

Barcelona, Spain

Working on Unannounced IP

Create concepts of characters, weapons and

props

SEP 2019 - NOV 2021

Berlin, Germany Wor

2D GAME ARTIST, KOLIBRI

Working on Idle Miner Tycoon

Create concepts and illustrations of offers, characters, backgrounds and game assets

JAN 2018 - APR 2019

JUNIOR 2D CONCEPT ARTIST, GAMELOFT

Danang, Vietnam

Working on N.O.V.A. Legacy
Create concept art and character designs

Drawing promotional illustrations

JUNE 2017 - DEC 2017

Trondheim, Norway

DEC 2017 FRE

FREELANCER, PROUDER AS

Drawing logos for high school-graduates

LANGUAGES

Norwegian Native English Fluent French Bilingual

EDUCATION

AUG 2013 - JUNE 2016

HEDMARK UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES,

DEPT. HAMAR

Bachelor in Digital Art and Design

AUG 2010 - JUNE 2013

PORSGRUNN HIGH SCHOOL

General studies with specialization in art

REFERENCES

Hugo Maximiliano Cadiz

Studio Lead Artist at Gameloft

E-mail:

teseo_arcadio@hotmail.com

Phone +84 96 390 17 57

KEY SKILLS

SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY

Character design
Illustration

Basic Unity

Concept art
Animal & creature design

Basic Autodesk Maya

Adobe Photoshop CC

Basic Adobe After Effects

Game assets

Basic Adobe Flash